{
    "id": "33695cac1b004bf3b538627fd6484eaa",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is a ………………………… old lady.",
            "description": "Respectable means worthy of respect. ",
            "answers": [
                "respectful",
                "respectable"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is very …………………………. I am sure he will succeed in life.",
            "description": "Industrious means skillful.",
            "answers": [
                "industrial",
                "industrious"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must learn to …………………………. yourself to changing circumstances.",
            "description": "To adapt is to adjust.",
            "answers": [
                "adapt",
                "adopt"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How long have you ………………………. in bed?",
            "description": "Lain is the past participle of to lie. ",
            "answers": [
                "lied",
                "lay",
                "lain"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The project will require a …………………………….. amount of money.",
            "description": "Considerable means huge. ",
            "answers": [
                "considerable",
                "considerate"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ……………………………. and lent me his car when I requested him to.",
            "description": "Considerate means thoughtful of others' feelings. ",
            "answers": [
                "considerable",
                "considerate"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The speech was …………………………… uninspiring.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "fairly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The soldiers fired …………………………….. causing several civilians to die.",
            "description": "Indiscriminately means thoughtlessly. ",
            "answers": [
                "discriminately",
                "indiscriminately"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She sat there, deep in …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thinking",
                "thought"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A good leader should be …………………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "apathetic",
                "sympathetic",
                "empathetic"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a …………………………… criminal.",
            "description": "A convicted criminal is one who is found guilty of committing a crime. ",
            "answers": [
                "convinced",
                "convicted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The view from the window was ……………………………",
            "description": "Expansive means having a wide range. ",
            "answers": [
                "expensive",
                "expansive",
                "expulsive"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}